State of Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions 6310
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
State of Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions
1992-2016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
State of Connecticut Board of Labor Relations
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
6310
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Decisions.
7130151
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, September 08, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 31, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective labor agreements -- Connecticut -- Officials and employees; State of Connectivut Board of Labor.
7130151
- Decision no.3000 (1992:Apr. 22) - no.3646 (1998:Dec. 15). (Box 1)
  - Decisions 3000 - 3050, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    April 22, 1992 - October 26, 1992
  - Decisions 3053 - 3072, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    November 9, 1992 - January 25, 1993
  - Decisions 3076 - 3097, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    February 10, 1993 - April 16, 1993
  - Decisions 3100 - 3119, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    April 27, 1993 - June 15, 1993
  - Decisions 3126 - 3146, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    July 16, 1993 - November 4, 1993
  - Decisions 3147 - 3175, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    November 5, 1993 - January 13, 1994
  - Decisions 3186 - 3216, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    February 25, 1994 - May 19, 1994
  - Decisions 3216A - 3240, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    June 6, 1994 - September 28, 1994
  - Decisions 3243 - 3261A, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    October 21, 1994 - April 25, 1995
  - Decisions 3268 - 3298, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    January 13, 1995 - May 10, 1995
  - Decisions 3309 - 3335, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    May 26, 1995 - September 19, 1995
  - Decisions 3336 - 3379, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    January 17, 1996 - April 2, 1996
  - Decisions 3356 - 3379, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Decisions 3383 - 3423, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    April 10, 1996 - July 24, 1996
  - Decisions 3424 - 3447, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    July 29, 1996 - October 27, 1996
  - Decisions 3448 - 3484, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    October 22, 1996 - March 24, 1997
  - Decisions 3486 - 3499, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    March 27, 1997 - April 28, 1997
  - Decisions 3500 - 3526, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    April 29, 1997 - August 28, 1997
  - Decisions 3527 - 3575, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    August 28, 1997 - February 19, 1998
  - Decisions 3576 - 3597, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    February 19, 1998 - May 7, 1998
  - Decisions 3600 - 3646, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    May 13, 1998 - December 15, 1998
- Decision no.3648 (1998:Dec. 17) - no.4319 (2008:Apr. 28). (Box 2)
  - Decisions 3648 - 3666, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    December 17, 1998 - March 10, 1999
  - Decisions 3667 - 3698, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    March 10, 1999 - June 9, 1999
  - Decisions 3701 - 3724, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    June 10, 1999 - August 31, 1999
  - Decisions 3725 - 3748, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    September 2, 1999 - January 27, 2000
  - Decisions 3749 - 3778, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    February 2, 2000 - July 6, 2000
  - Decisions 3779 - 3797, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    July 7, 2000 - October 19, 2000
  - Decisions 3803 - 3846, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    January 12, 2001 - October 24, 2001
  - Decisions 3847 - 3898, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    October 25, 2001 - February 13, 2003
  - Decisions 3902 - 3945, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    March 6, 2003 - February 26, 2004
  - Decisions 3946 - 3977, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    February 27, 2004 - June 4, 2004
  - Decisions 3978 - 3999, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    June 4, 2004 - September 1, 2004
  - Decisions 4000 - 4030, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    September 13, 2004 - March 16, 2005
  - Decisions 4031 - 4065, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    March 16, 2005 - July 27, 2005
  - Decisions 4066 - 4088, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    July 28, 2005 - September 30, 2005
  - Decisions 4089 - 4105, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    September 30, 2005 - December 21, 2005
  - Decisions 4106 - 4128, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    December 29, 2005 - March 2, 2006
  - Decisions 4129 - 4158, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    March 3, 2006 - May 1, 2006
  - Decisions 4159 - 4207, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    May 12, 2006 - February 16, 2007
  - Decisions 4208 - 4233, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    February 16, 2007 - April 12, 2007
  - Decisions 4235 - 4258, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    April 20, 2007 - September 26, 2007
  - Decisions 4259 - 4280, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    September 27, 2007 - January 9, 2008
  - Decisions 4281 - 4319, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    January 18, 2008 - April 28, 2008
- Decision no.4320 (2008:Apr. 28) - no.4809 (2015:Mar. 31). (Box 3)
  - Decisions 4320 - 4336, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    April 29, 2008 - August 26, 2008
  - Decisions 4337 - 4356, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    September 8, 2008 - December 1, 2008
  - Decisions 4357 - 4376, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    December 18, 2008 - March 19, 2009
  - Decisions 4377 - 4399, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    March 23, 2009 - July 28, 2009
  - Decisions 4400 - 4427, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    August 13, 2009 - December 10, 2009
  - Decisions 4428 - 4453, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    December 16, 2009 - March 12, 2010
  - Decisions 4454 - 4472, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    March 17, 2010 - July 20, 2010
  - Decisions 4473 - 4493, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    July 28, 2010 - February 11, 2011
  - Decisions 4494 - 4524, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    February 17, 2011 - May 13, 2011
  - Decisions 4525 - 4537, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    May 18, 2011 - July 13, 2011
  - Decisions 4538 - 4554, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    July 19, 2011 - September 23, 2011
  - Decisions 4555 - 4566, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    September 27, 2011 - December 1, 2011
  - Decisions 4568 - 4588, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    December 7, 2011 - March 8, 2012
  - Decisions 4589 - 4602, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    March 13, 2012 - May 16 2012
  - Decisions 4603 - 4616, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    June 1, 2012 - August 30, 2012
  - Decisions 4617 - 4626, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    September 24, 2012 - December 18, 2012
  - Decisions 4627 - 4643, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    December 19, 2012 - March 12, 2013
  - Decisions 4646 - 4656, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    March 12, 2013 - March 28, 2013
  - Decisions 4657 - 4671, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    April 3, 2013 - July 2, 2013
  - Decisions 4672 - 4882, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    August 1, 2013 - October 8, 2013
  - Decisions 4683 - 4698, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    October 21, 2013 - February 24, 2014
  - Decisions 4699 - 4713, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    March 3, 2014 - March 18, 2014
  - Decisions 4729A, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    May 14, 2014
  - Decisions 4736 - 4749, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    May 16, 2014 - July 18, 2014
  - Decisions 4750 - 4757, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    July 21, 2014 - August 29, 2014
  - Decisions 4758 - 4771, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    September 16, 2014 - December 30, 2014.
  - Decisions 4772 - 4797, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    January 7, 2015 - March 11, 2015.
  - Decisions 4798 - 4809, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    March 13, 2015 - March 31, 2015.
- Decision no.4844 (2015:Oct. 8) - no.4888 (2016:July 26). (Box 4)
  - Decisions 4844 - 4856, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    October 8 - December 30, 2015
  - Decisions 4857 - 4871, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    January 5 - February 25, 2016
  - Decisions 4872 - 4888, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    March 1 - April 6, 2016
  - Decisions 4889 - 4899, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    April 13 - May 19, 2016
  - Decisions 4901 - 4913, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    May 25 - July 26, 2016